{
    "subject": "resource/Pythagoras",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Anaximander",
    "human_readable": "Pythagoras was influenced by Anaximander.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9479684829711914,
            "question": "What impact did Anaximander's ideas have on Pythagoras?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8716501593589783,
            "question": "Who influenced Pythagoras?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8180009722709656,
            "question": "How did Anaximander's teachings shape Pythagoras' work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7961143851280212,
            "question": "What is the connection between Pythagoras and Anaximander?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.79285728931427,
            "question": "Can you identify a philosophical relationship between Pythagoras and Anaximander?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6490929126739502,
            "question": "Was Pythagoras influenced by other philosophers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6484517455101013,
            "question": "Name a philosopher who influenced Pythagoras."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6040171384811401,
            "question": "Who was Anaximander?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34908148646354675,
            "question": "Did Pythagoras learn from any ancient thinkers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.088811494410038,
            "question": "Who were some of the key figures that influenced Greek philosophy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pythagoras was influenced by Anaximander.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8121_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Pythagoras learn from any ancient thinkers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8121_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Anaximander?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8121_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a philosopher who influenced Pythagoras.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8121_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8121_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Pythagoras attended Anaximander's lectures on Miletus and learned about Anaximander's interest in geometry and cosmology, which influenced Pythagoras' ideas about mathematics as well (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8121/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Pythagoras was influenced by Anaximander. This is evident from multiple references in the provided texts, such as noting that Pythagoras attended Anaximander's lectures and learned about geometry and cosmology from him, which influenced Pythagoras' own views on mathematics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}